[
  {
    "idQuestion": "1",
    "answerCorrect": "D"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "2",
    "answerCorrect": "C"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "3",
    "answerCorrect": "D"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "4",
    "answerCorrect": "C"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "5",
    "answerCorrect": "C"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "6",
    "answerCorrect": "D"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "7",
    "answerCorrect": "B"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "8",
    "answerCorrect": "C"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "9",
    "answerCorrect": "A"
  },
  {
    "idQuestion": "10",
    "answerCorrect": "B"
  }
]